<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2024 on NEU CTF Club</title>
    <link>https://neu-ctf.club/tags/2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2024 on NEU CTF Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    <atom:link href="https://neu-ctf.club/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTF Thyme</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_thyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_thyme/</guid>
      <description>Hi Hackers!! Hungry for more CTFs? Want some real competition experience to put on your resume that employers will eat up? Come join CTF club and NU WiCyS for a friendsgiving feast at CTF Thyme!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
=======
>>>>>>> main
    <atom:link href="https://neu-ctf.club/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTF Thyme</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_thyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_thyme/</guid>
      <description>Hi Hackers!! Hungry for more CTFs? Want some real competition experience to put on your resume that employers will eat up? Come join CTF club and NU WiCyS for a friendsgiving feast at CTF Thyme!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#5:  Operation Offline</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm5/</guid>
      <description>Hi Hackers!! Our LAST GM of the whole semester is already here !! Plan, coordinate, and execute a bank heist with us- and perhaps win some gift cards if you make it out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#4: Exploit Manor</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm4/</guid>
      <description>Hi Hackers! Looking for a spooky scary time? Want to try your hand at some tricks and get rewarded with treats? Come to our GM to escape a haunted house by solving CTF challenges, and eat lots of candy along the way!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#3: Ownlympics</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm3/</guid>
      <description>Hi Hackers!!! Want to get better at CTFs? Want to train your problem solving muscles? Get big and strong for the winter bulk? Come to our next General Meeting to train, then compete in a fun event to win gift cards!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#2: Game Night</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm2/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE GAMBLING! If you love gambling — and/or learning about offensive cybersecurity — come to our SECOND general meeting of the year, Game Night! Yes yes yes, there will be challenges … but, for each challenge you solve, you will have the chance to try your luck ;) maybe you’ll win a Starbucks gift card .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versus CTF</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_versus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_versus/</guid>
      <description>GET READY FOR VERSUS CTF with Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute’s Security Club!! Join us SATURDAY, SEPT 21, 12PM in Shillman 220 for free catered food, prizes and surprises, plenty of challenges, and fun teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#1: Wild West</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/fa24_gm1/</guid>
      <description>Hackers, this town ain’t big enough for the two of us. On Tuesday, Sept. 10 at 6pm, we will be giddying up for a new year of CTF! Come prepared with a laptop and your best problem solving skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEATF</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_seatf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_seatf/</guid>
      <description>Hi hackers! Join CTF Club, NU WiCyS, and NU Security for the sequel to the fall’s SUB-Z3R0: SeaTF! This CTF is open to any and all interested undergraduate students, regardless of experience!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#6: Bunny Bounty</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm6/</guid>
      <description>Hi hackers! Join us NEXT WEDNESDAY as we fight to the death for the easter bunny’s delightful children…. I mean challenges. There’s lots of hidden challenges and flags waiting for you to crack open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#5: Ghidra Guidance</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm5/</guid>
      <description>Hi hackers! Join CTFC x WiCyS THIS WEDNESDAY as we hone in on Ghidra and its elite capabilities. Developed by the NSA and released as an open-source software, Ghidra has broken down barriers to entry in the field of reverse engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#4: Osint Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm4/</guid>
      <description>hi hackers! Join us as we use our ultimate stalking… I mean investigation skills with the OSINT framework. We’ll go over some tried and true strategies for information-gathering. In today’s data-driven world, knowledge truly is power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#3: P.S. I Love CTFs</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm3/</guid>
      <description>Hi hackers! with Valentine’s Day around the corner, the CTF Club would like to invite you to our P.S. I Love You… I meant CTFs event next week on Feb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#2: Crypto Trail</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm2/</guid>
      <description>Hey hackers! Get ready for an EXCITING ADVENTURE this upcoming Monday! Join us for ROUND 2 of our thrilling treasure hunt where you’ll follow a trail of cryptic challenges leading to a DELICIOUS, MYSTERIOUS prizes&amp;hellip; oooo ahhhh&amp;hellip; Trust, this event is a fan favorite!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month[0] CTF</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_month0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_month0/</guid>
      <description>Our first CTF Competition of the semester will be January 31st! Come celebrate completing the first month of 2024 with us by solving challenges and possibly winning Amazon gift cards!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM#1: Murder, Mystery, &amp; CTFs</title>
      <link>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://neu-ctf.club/events/sp24_gm1/</guid>
      <description>Hi hackers! We’re back and better than ever! Join us this Wednesday 1/10 for a Clue inspired murder mystery challenge. We need your help in catching the killer here on NEU&amp;rsquo;s campus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
